proxyusa.org 2013-11-27

# Proxyusa.org privacy policy

Privacy Policy for Proxyusa.org

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@Proxyusa.org .

At Proxyusa.org, the privacy of our visitors is very much important to us.   
Proxyusa.org provides this privacy policy to inform you of our policies regarding the collection,use and disclosure of personal information we receive when you visit the Proxyusa.org website and when you use any part of our website.

this privacy policy applies only to information  that you provide us through the service when you use, access, download or use any content appearing on Proxyusa.org site or offered by us through the service, or that we collect on your behalf as part of the service.  
this privacy policy may be amended or updated from time to time.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, Proxyusa.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
Proxyusa.org does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, adversal.com, cpxinteractive.com  .

Google, adversal as a third party vendors, use cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Proxyusa.org send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Proxyusa.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Proxyusa.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
